Long time no silicone video and that's why we're here for another Futurax try on.
I have a silicone bodysuit with as you can see thick boobs here.
Though these are not filled out. They're really squishy and empty.
And we have this dress. Yes it's a dress.
So this dress it's basically a nurse outfit.
And again we have the bust area here which is a bit padded this time and in the back
I don't know if you can see it
We have a hole in the dress and you will see in a second how I am going to manage this
Okay, it was actually
rather easy to get into this so I looped my legs the outside of my legs and
My back my body my hips and then I pulled
everything up that it was in my waist like the whole dress and then I put the
arms because it is neck entry and it is heavy but that's the look and I know
you've been waiting for this that's the behind look I put on these really cool
shoe tights whatever it's a one-piece and I think it's a great match for the
rid of the dress and also to be YouTube friendly and safe here on the internet. The fit is so good
I know with a lot of silicone pieces it's hit or miss one size whatever but this just fits so good
it's so tight it's actually figure shaping effects or shapewear because it snatches everything in
place I can feel that the arms are really tight and also the neck is really tight of course
everything is stretchy so I squeezed through that yes and also with the lines here it looks
even slimmer optically the waist is snatched it fits everywhere my bust is bigger because
as I showed you in the intro the bust is standing by itself because it has a bit of padding it is
thicker here so I'm not filling out everything but still it looks great everything stands
yay for the shapewear effect we have these lines here which are almost like I don't know piping or
something these are design elements I haven't seen them on catsuits yet I think they're really nice
because they add more depth and more 3d layering here also again the shape of them just adds to
overall waist effect here and these are also here at the arm so it's almost like
they are imitating hemlines again in the back here so I really like this if you
want a matching hood I can recommend this because we have the crosses here
again it is available in black and red by now so not only pink but you know the
matching color and the dress itself is also available in pink and in turquoise
And I do have a discount code with which you can save a few bucks, so check that out too.
But I'm going to put on the bodysuit next.
I already switched into a whole style, not just the bodysuit, but first,
let me tell you something about a sponsor for today's video, Johnny Dib.
And you may be wondering, what? Why are you partnering up with a Dib company?
Funny story actually, let me tell you.
They were looking for a blue haired model and YouTube recommended them one of my videos.
so they wrote me an email if I would be interested in producing an advertisement
video for them and that email was in my spam folder. I didn't answer for I don't
know two weeks or something but then they commented on the one of my YouTube
videos and I found the email and so the whole collaboration started and I made
two whole ad videos for them. Johnny Depp is a young German brand for handmade
gourmet sauces. They are produced by Das Pfefferhaus which ships to many
countries of the EU. So I will put a link down in the description text and you can
check it out yourself. There are two varieties mango chill and barbecue chill
and they have two different levels of spiciness. So barbecue is a bit more
spicy and I have to say I'm not the biggest barbecue fan and it was actually
too spicy for me. Yeah I prefer mango I love this one it's so so good. For me you
can try both and then tell me if I'm just whiny and it's not even that spicy
you don't have to store them in the fridge but pro tip in summer put them in
the fridge because it's so great to dip your nachos into a cold dip it's really
refreshing I tried it I was surprised there's a bundle available of the two
varieties for a special price so check out a link in the description text and
thanks for Johnny dip for partnering up with me now back to the actual styling
Okay I've put on a whole styling already
I will show you the bodysuit without the skirt later on
But I thought let's style it first
I think it's a cool look
And to use the bodysuit just as a top basically
Is a way to make it less fetishy
If you want to wear it out in public
But are not comfortable enough to just wear out a whole fetish
Or if I just put normal clothes on top of it
It is again a neck entry here
so squeezing through that and the cuts with the cheekbones especially is
basically the same as the catsuits from Fittorax which I like because you know
what you get also we have these 3d kind of hemlines here at the arms and also at
legs and I left it matte but of course you can shine it up then you get a
different look Fittorax also set this hood along which is one size again I put
it on the styrofoam head and it has a curious mouth opening here with it comes a lock and the
key and now you have to insert this lock into the mask well i should probably put the key in it
to rotate it in place yeah now it's closed and you can't really open it i can try and push it out
like from the inside doesn't doesn't work so you actually need the key to remove this again
but i feel like a magician there was also this shroud which is actually made of latex
it's an outfit and you have to put it
around the head like this so that's how it looks together please help me out in the comments is it
a shroud is it a veil I'm not sure I know the German word which is habitat but not the English
one anyway I think it's a nice black and white look to be honest it's rather long too and we
the combination of latex and silicon here. Quite interesting. If you combine these two materials
please make sure to wash them both afterwards really carefully and separate and also store
them separately so the silicone does not damage the latex. Alright I promised you I will show you
the bodysuit. It's full glory without the outfit so let me get undressed. A sentence I rarely say
on YouTube and I hope YouTube does not complain about the bodysuit because I had problems in the
past with showing a leg cut a high leg cut on bodysuits which is really annoying
that's why I'm doing this very shortly at the end I do love the cut from the booty part
we have this 3d shaped butt here again which I think makes the booty look great
and again the high leg so this is a bodysuit rather simple elegant hope you enjoyed it
i hope you like it write it down in the comments below which your favorite item was and also check
out the links i will link for turrox i will link johnny dip i will see you in the next video check
my Patreon out, my Instagram and all the stuff. Alright, see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!